Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Office of the Dean of Students Records, 1915-2012
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1915-2012, UWM Archival Collection 48; 28.2 cubic ft. (40 boxes) 5 digital text files (2 MB)
  - 1. Student Organization Files, 1915-2010
    - Mid-Continental Model United Nations Program, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Middle East Coalition Against Violence and Racism, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Military Council at UWM, 1962-1985 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Milwaukee Adventure Gaming Society, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Milwaukee Alliance, 1973-1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Milwaukee Area Jewish Independent Coalition, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Milwaukee Area Nonviolent Direct Action Committee, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Milwaukee Betar, 1974-1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Milwaukee Cardinals Pep Club, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Milwaukee Citizen's Drug Prevention Ad Hoc Committee, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Milwaukee Coalition for Choice at UWM, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Milwaukee Committee for American-Soviet Friendship, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Milwaukee Educational Society, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Milwaukee Graduate Assistants Association, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - Milwaukee Hunger Hike, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Milwaukee Intercollegiate Civil Liberties Union, 1957-1959 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Milwaukee Liberation Front, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Milwaukee Organizing Committee, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Milwaukee People's Office, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Milwaukee Rebirth Association, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Milwaukee Road Review, 1979-1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Milwaukee Square Dancers, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Milwaukee Student Chapter of the APA, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Milwaukee Student Peace Union, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Milwaukee Students Association, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Milwaukee Undergraduate Review, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Milwaukee Women's Rugby Football Club, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Minorities for Wood, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Minority Business Students Association, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Minority Coalition, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Mixed Chorus, 1958-1962 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Mixed Media, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Model United Nations, 1965-1968 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Mondale/Ferraro, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Montessorian, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Mortar Board, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Mortar Board, 1975-1979 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Motor Sports Association, 1967-1974 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Movement for a New Congress, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Movimiento Estudiantil Chicano de Aztlan, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - MSW Club at UWM, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Mu Beta Sigma, undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Mu Epsilon Pi, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Mu Kappa Tau (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - Mural, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Music Educator's National Conference, 1957-1963 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Music Entertainment Association, 1991-1994 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Music From Almost Yesterday, 1979-1985 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Music Students Association, 1957-1960 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Music Therapy Organization, 1969-1990 (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - Music Through Action, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Music With Percussion Ensemble, 1974-1990 (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Muslim Youth, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - NA Recovery at UWM, 1989-1993 (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - NAACP, 1957-1994 (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - Narcotics Anonymous, 1978-1982 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Nation Every Nation, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 93)
    - National and International Student Congress, 1973-1977 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - National Art Education Association (NAEA), 1976-1986 (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - National Association of Black Journalists, 1988-1992 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - National Broadcasting Society - Alpha Epsilon Rho, 1980-1993 (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - National Campus Film Network/Dream on Film Series, 1982-1990 (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - National Collegiate Players, 1963-1972 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - National Honor Society, 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - National Jazz Fraternity, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - National Organization for Women (NOW), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 98)
    - National Society of Pershing Rifles, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - National Student Association, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Navigators at UWM, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 99)
    - Negative Movement, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - New Age Bible Study, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - New Age Party, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - New American Movement
      - 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - undated (Box 18, Folder 100)
    - New Community at UWM, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 101)
    - New Directions, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 102)
    - New Edition, 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 103)
    - New Era, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 104)
    - New Fenians, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - New Media Club, 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 105)
    - New Party at UWM, 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 106)
    - Newman Club, 1957-1970 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Nigerian Student Organization, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - None of the Above, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 107)
    - Non-Partisan Party, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 108)
    - Notable Organization for Valued Academics (ANOVA), 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 109)
    - Northpoint Junior Investment Club, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - NSA Club of UWM, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Nu Digamma Phi (New Warrior Fraternity), 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 110)
    - Nurses Professional Organization, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - OA at UWM, 1987-1993 (Box 18, Folder 111)
    - October 23 Coalition, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Off Campus Student Residence Location Study, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Ojibwemo Society, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 112)
    - Omega Club, 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Omega Community Service Organization, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Omega Pearl Club, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Omicron Delta Kappa, 1951-1953 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Omicron Mu, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Oratorio Chorus, 1958-1977 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Order of Artus, 1959-1961 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Organ Guild, 1959-1977 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Organization for Students of Objectivism, 1967-1971 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Organization for the Learning Disabled at UWM, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Organization of Justice, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 113)
    - Organization of Professionals Help, Crisis Referral Line, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 114)
    - Organization of School Psychology, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Organized Rock Climbers, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - ORO - Macedonian Folk Ensemble, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Othello Club at UWM, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Orthodox Campus Fellowship, 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 115)
    - Orthodox Christian Fellowship, 1970-1987 (Box 18, Folder 116)
    - Out To Lunch Party, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Outing Club, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Outing Council, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Padarewski Club, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Pail and Shovel, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 117)
    - Pakistani Student Association, 1980-1988 (Box 18, Folder 118)
    - Paleontological Society of UWM, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 119)
    - Palestine Liberation Support Committee, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Panhellenic Ball Reports, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Panhellenic Council
      - 1960-1971 (Box 5, Folder 65)
      - Housing, 1958-1970 (Box 5, Folder 66)
      - Rush, 1952-1967 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Panther Booster Club, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Panther Courier, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Panther Dive Club, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 120)
    - Panther Football Club, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 121)
    - Panther Herald, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 122)
    - Panther Party of UWM, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Panther Pep Club, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Panther Platoon, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 123)
    - Panther Publishers, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 124)
    - Panther Soccer Club, 1970-1976 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Panther Travel, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 125)
    - Panthers for Pep, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Para-Psychological Society, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Pat Paulsen Intranational Peace Party, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Pax Christi Catholic Peace Movement, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Peace Through Law, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Peak Night
      - 1947-1964 (Box 11, Folder 37-39)
      - Programs, 1938-1967 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Pedal for the Homeless, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 126)
    - People for Dennis Conta, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - People for Improved Education, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - People for Unspecified Stuff, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 127)
    - People United for Integration & Quality Education, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - People's Bicentennial Commission, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Peoples Consciousness Front, 1987-1992 (Box 18, Folder 128)
    - People's Daily World Readers Club, 1981-1988 (Box 18, Folder 129)
    - People's Party Student Organization, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - People's Peace Treaty, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Pershing Rifles
      - 1958-1970 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      - 1958-1990 (Box 18, Folder 130)
    - Phantasy Films, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Pharmaceutical Society, 1957-1974 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Phi Alpha Theta, 1953-1962 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Phi Beta Kappa
      - 1964, 1973-1978, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 43)
      - 1973-1974, undated (Box 18, Folder 131)
    - Phi Beta Rho, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Phi Chi Theta, 1966-1973 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Phi Delta Delta, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Phi Delta Epsilon, 1960-1967 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Phi Delta Kappa, 1958-1967 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Phi Eta Sigma, 1956-1963 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Phi Gamma Delta, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Phi Gamma Nu, 1966-1976 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Phi Kappa Phi, 1961-1990 (Box 18, Folder 132)
    - Phi Kappa Sigma, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Phi Lambda Theta, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Phi Mu, 1957-1974 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Phi Mu Alpha Sinfonia, 1957-1975 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Phi Mu Sigma, 1956-1970 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Phi Sigma Delta
      - 1956-1969 (Box 11, Folder 46)
      - 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Phi Sigma Epsilon
      - 1950-1969 (Box 11, Folder 47-48)
      - 1957-1973 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Phi Sigma Kappa, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Phi Sigma Sigma
      - 1955-1974 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - 1960-1970 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Phi Tau, 1968-1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Philatelic Society, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Philocophia Club, 1917-1956 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Philocophia Club, Scrapbook, 1945-1957 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Philosophical Circle, 1959-1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Philosophers Anonymous, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 133)
    - Philosophical Association at UWM, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 134)
    - Philosophy Club, 1960-1963 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Photographers for a Democratic Society, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Physical Education Majors and Minors Club, 1961-1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Pi Lambda Theta, 1959-1963 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Pi Lambda Theta
      - 1959-1963 (Box 11, Folder 52)
      - 1959-1991 (Box 18, Folder 135)
    - Pi Sigma Alpha, 1976-1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Pi Sigma Epsilon, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Pinkos, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Planning Documents, 1981-1985 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Player's Association, 1979-1986 (Box 18, Folder 136)
    - Playrs 'O, 1988-1995 (Box 18, Folder 137)
    - Poetry Society, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Policies and Regulations Governing Greek Houses and Lodges, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Polish Club, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Political Action and Arts Network, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 138)
    - Political Awareness Group Against Noninvolvement, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 139)
    - Political Items Collectors Klub, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Political Rights Defense Fund, 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Political Science Association, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Pompon Girls, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Portrait of an Artist, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 140)
    - Positive Leadership Under Students, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 141)
    - Potomac Film Productions, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Pre-Teachers Organization at UWM, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 142)
    - Pre-Theological Club, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Pre-Veterinarian Club, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 143)
    - Prem Kanta, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Press Club at UWM, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Prime Time Backgammon Club, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Prime Time for Women, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Prism, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 144)
    - Probe, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - ProBuColls, 1966-1981 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Professional and Academic League, 1967-1971 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Professionals in Training, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 145)
    - Progress Through Action, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 146)
    - Progressive Iranian Muslim Students, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Progressive List for Peace, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 147)
    - Progressive Programmers, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 148)
    - Progressive Programmers of Wisconsin, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 149)
    - Progressive Student Forum, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Progressive Students Alliance, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Project Black
      - 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 57)
      - 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Project Concern, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Pro-Life at UWM, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 150)
    - Protest Literature, 1940, 1968-1974 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Psi Chi, 1957-1963 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Psi World Vanguard of Wisconsin, UWM Chapter, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Psychology Club at UWM, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 151)
    - Publications Committee
      - Accounts, 1925-1952 (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
      - Minutes, 1933-1956 (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
    - Purin Hall Residents Association, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 152)
    - Purin Hall Tenants Union, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Pythagorean Club, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Que's, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Racquetball Club at UWM, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Radical Education Committee, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Ranger Rifle Club, 1957-1990 (Box 18, Folder 153)
    - Rap House, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Rationalist Church of America, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Ray Mendoza Defense Fund, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Reaganbusters, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Real Investment & Speculation Klub, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Recreational Facilities, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Reforms According to the Voice of Everyone (RAVE), 1993 (Box 18, Folder 154)
    - Refuse and Resist!, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 155)
    - Registered Nurse Association, 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Relaxation Club, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 156)
    - Relevant Action Party, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Religious Studies Association at UWM, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Renaissance Art Guild, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Renegade Time Lords, 1983-1993 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Reorganized Latter Day Saint Student Centre, 1988-1992 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - The Representative, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Representative Party, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Representative Speakers Bureau, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Republican Unit, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Residence Hall Visitation Experiments, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Revolutionary Student Brigade, 1972-1977 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Riflemen at UWM, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Robert Kennedy Memorial, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Roger Faulkner for Senate, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Roscoe, 1985-1989 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - ROTC Organizations, 1958-1968 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Rowing Club, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Rush Booklets, 1957-1968 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Russ Feingold for U.S. Senate at UWM, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - S.O.R.A.L.E., 1976-1982 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Safewalk, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - St. Paul Christian Methodist Episcopal Mission, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Sammy Younge Brigade, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Sandburg Commons Advisory Board, 1986-1990 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Sandburg Hall, 1971-1987 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Sane Nuclear Policy Committee, 1958-1965 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - SARUP Soccer Club, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - SARUP Student Society, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Scabbard and Blade, 1958-1987 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Scholars for Mental Vacuity, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - School of Allied Health Professions Student Council, 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - School of Education Club, 1961-1963 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Schweitzer Club, 1961-1968 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Science Fiction Services, 1976-1987 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Science of Creation Club, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Scientific Debate Invitational, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - "Scoop" Pamphlets, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Screaming Eagle Arts, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Scuba Club, 1980-1984 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Secondary Division, 1925-1960 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Secondary Education Club, 1957-1963 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Section .09(5) Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Segregated Fee Advisory Committee
      - 1969-1976 (Box 6, Folder 55)
      - Athletic Fees, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 56)
      - Minutes, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 57-58)
      - Procedures, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Self-Actualizing Student Association, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Semper Fidelis Society, 1977-1987 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Senior Class
      - 1915-1956 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - 1958-1966 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Senior Classes, 1958-1973 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Seniors for a Meaningful Class Gift, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - S.H.A.P.E. (Students Helping Achieve Political Ethics), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Shepard Alumni House, 1945?-1961 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Shepherds, 1986-1992 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Shorts Film Society, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Sigma Alpha Eta, 1957-1963 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Sigma Delta Chi, 1964-1972 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Sigma Delta Omega, 1957-1961, undated (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Sigma Delta Pi, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Sigma Delta Psi, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Sigma Delta Sigma, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Sigma Epsilon Ksi, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Sigma Epsilon Sigma, 1964-1983 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Sigma Iota Lambda, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Sigma Kappa Alpha, 1950-1957 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Sigma Nu Fraternity, Seventy-fifth Anniversary Plaque, 1973, 4" x 4" pewter plaque (Box 40)
    - Sigma Omicron Delta, 1954-1958 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Sigma Pi, 1964-1970 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Sigma Sigma Sigma
      - 1957-1963 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - 1957-1987 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Sigma Tau Delta, 1960-1970 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Sigma Tau Gamma, 1973-1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Sigma XI, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Simply A Social Organization, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Sisters in Struggle, 1992-1995 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Six Fathom Club, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Slavic Club, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Slumber Party, 1985-1989 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Smiths Fan Club, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Snide, Humor Magazine, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Snowboarders Club of UWM, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Social Action for Gender Equality, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Social Democratic Party, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Social Event Summaries, 1959-1972 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Social Psychology Coalition, 1982-1985 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Social Work Club, 1957-1968 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Socialists, 1975-1987 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Society for a Better Society, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Society for Creative Anachronism, Inc., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Society for Ecological Enthusiasts, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Society for Formal Discussion, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Society for Study of Visual Anthropology, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Society for the Advancement of Future Minority Doctors, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Society for the Advancement of Management
      - 1957-1967 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - 1959-1973 (Box 6, Folder 83)
      - Financial Records, 1958-1963 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Society for the Investigation of Marxism, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Society of Engineers & Applied Scientists, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Society of Individualists, 1959-1962 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Society of Professional Engineers, 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Society of Professional Journalists, 1963-1993 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Society of Professional Journalists, 1965-1974 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Society of Student Engineers, 1947-1965 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Society of Typographic Arts, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Society of Urbanologists, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Society to Clothe Animals, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Sociocultural Research Center, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Socratic Society at UWM, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Solidarity Day, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Song of the T'ai-chi T'u, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Sororities, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Sound Board, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Southeast Transit Research Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - Spanish and Portuguese Club, 1958-1971 (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - Spanish Club, 1958-1964 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Spectrum, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Spinnakers Sailing Club, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Sport Parachute Club, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Sports Car Club
      - 1958-1967 (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Spuds - A Daga - Epsilon, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Square One, 1983-1987 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Stamp Out Petty Politics, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Standard Oil Teaching Awards, 1966-1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - S.T.A.R. (Students Taking an Active Role), 1994 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - States Rights Association, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Stomp! Productions, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Stonerock Festival Concert, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Stop Waste in S.A., 1987 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Stowell House Association, 1957-1968 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Student Action Party, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Student Activities Caucus, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Student Advisory Committee for the Music Department, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Student Affiliates of the American Chemical Society
      - 1965-1968 (Box 12, Folder 39)
      - 1968-1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Student Association
      - 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 1-5)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Academic Policy, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Administrative, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Administrative Appointments, Task Force and Working Groups, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Aeronautics and Aerospace Organization, Internal Audit Report and Correspondence, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Agendas, 2005-2007 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Burma Refugee Relief Coalition, 2002-2003 (Box 35, Folder 3)